Hello everyone and welcome back
to another live stream.
Today we're gonna be diving deep into some old school retro
gaming with four iconic Nintendo handhelds,
a Maroon Nintendo Game Boy color,
a Red Game Boy Advance sp a White Nintendo, DSI
and a Nintendo three DS xl.
Each handheld has its own conditions, its own story.
So if you'd like to learn more
and check out to see if these consoles look interesting
to you, be sure to stick around and keep watching.
Let's go ahead and get started then.
So to get started, we're going to be talking about first
a Nintendo game Boy color.
So this Maroon Game Boy color was first released in Japan on
October 21st, 1998,
and then shortly afterwards in North America in November
of 1998, that same year.
This maroon edition definitely is an excellent condition
and also helps symbolize
and pop out some of the other colors on the console.
So talking about the console itself,
the shape it's in is in excellent shape.
However, there is a light scratch.
I think you can kind of see it on the camera right there on
the screen, as well
as then the barcode on the back is also not in the best
of shape, but can be easily replaced.
Tech-wise, it's powered by an eight bit Z 80 processor,
32 kilobytes of Ram.
Woo. You gotta be careful with that.
And features a vibrant one 60 by 1 44 pixel screen capable
of displaying up to 56 colors simultaneously,
which was very excellent tech for back at its day.
Uh, and also an interesting fact the game color was the
first Nintendo console to support backward compatibility.
Eh, eh, uh, the joke is that it's the first sequel
to its handheld consoles.
So, uh, dumb jokes aside, let's go ahead
and pop in the batteries to turn on the console.
And, oh, I forgot to mention,
the Battery Bay itself is in excellent shape
with no corrosion and no, uh, rust, as you can see.
Let's go ahead and put in some batteries.
And while I'm doing this, I'll go ahead
and answer a question.
Does the volume wheel work? Yes, yes, it does.
Let me go ahead and make sure that
that is working and test it for you.
Any other questions as well?
Does it come with a backlit screen? No.
So this is everything is stock in this
Nintendo game Boy color.
Um, there are no modifications done.
So yes, there are mods
and kits where you can actually replace the screen
with A LCD
or even like an LED screen, um, that will also fit natively
inside the Game Boy color.
And you can also replace the case as well
with your own case if you would like.
So essentially just taking out the internals.
Um, however, the shape of this case
is an excellent condition.
It's all stock, all the labels are even stock,
and it's kind of the little bit of the yellow wing
and kind of a little bit of the bumpy feeling
of the barcode, but, um, that can all be replaced easily.
So let's go ahead and get started.
So, initial conditions,
so the Game Boy screen does come on.
Um, I don't, let me make sure you can hear the sound.
Um, actually to do that, let's just pop in a copy
of Game Boy of Pokemon Crystal version.
And this is an, an American Nintendo game boy color.
So all the Game Boy colors are able
to play any kind of game from any region.
So the Nintendo Game Boy color is a region free console.
However, just keep in mind that, um, you know,
language barriers of course are going to be a thing.
So let's go ahead and turn this on with the copy of Game Boy
of, uh, Pokemon Crystal inside the game.
Lemme make sure you can hear the sound as well.
So I just saw a question about the volume.
Yeah, hopefully you can hear the sound.
Excellent. Okay. So as you can see, uh,
it's running a basically original copy
of Game Boy or of Pokemon Crystal.
Uh, of course it looks like the battery has run dry.
It was recently replaced, so I need to
start a new game save file.
So just to make sure that all the buttons are working
correctly, let's go ahead
and skip past, uh, professor Oak's dialogue.
I believe it's Professor Oak.
I don't think Elm comes in until later on in the game.
Uh, we're setting the clock. Yep, of course.
It's 10:00 AM actually, it is almost 10:00 AM So
while this is going on, I'll just read
another question in the chat.
Um, does Pokemon Crystal come with the game?
No, it does not. I apologize.
No, it, uh, it just, just to kind of show off
that the game is working and testing,
I have a few Pokemon games to kind of test out with,
but, uh, the games are not for sale, it's just
for the consoles themselves.
So as you can see, uh, the game is working perfectly fine.
Um, everything is working as intended.
So as we've kind of talked about, um, the,
the console condition, all the buttons are working properly.
Uh, the D pad's working select and starts.
It feels responsive. It doesn't feel
sticky, it doesn't feel stuck.
So it's a very good
and overall excellent condition console is the light.
Oh, the light is a little too bright. Okay.
Yeah, let me go ahead and turn off the light for now
so it's not as glaring on the screen.
Yeah, so that, that actually looks pretty,
pretty in excellent shape.
Excellent. Okay. So I'm not seeing any more questions,
just a lot of, uh, interested folks in it.
Okay, that's awesome. Glad to hear.
And you know, of course the, it's gonna slowly fade away.
So that is the Nintendo game boy color.
Okay, next, let's go ahead
and go up a generation, well,
I guess technically two generations
and talk about the next item, a Red Nintendo game.
Boy, advance. Sp So this one is not in as good
of a shape, unfortunately.
Um, it is however, a pretty big leap in terms of technology.
Uh, first we have the backlit screen where you can adjust it
by pressing the mi this kind of middle top button
to adjust the backlit screen.
Speaking of the screen, the condition is not that great,
unfortunately, so there's a lot of kind of, of scratches.
Uh, there's even like some kind
of a missing film on the screen right there, as you can see.
Um, and even kind of the siding,
there's like a bunch of wear.
So this would definitely need, if you would like
to play this natively, uh, a new case as well
as a new screen to talk about.
Buttons themselves, though, they feel great shape.
So the buttons are responsive, they don't stick, um,
it's just the shell and the screen are not in the best
of shape as you can kind of see all these scratches
on the top right there, as well as even the back, like some
of the labels where the Game Boy label is all faded
and a lot of the text is missing and some wear
and tear in the cartridge port.
But the cartridge port itself also looks in fantastic shape.
The shoulder buttons are in great shape, as well
as the different ports to be able
to plug in your light Game Boy Printer, the connection cable
or the serial port for the Game Boy
printer, if you would like to do so.
So the Nintendo Game Boy Advance.
Sp uh, if we talk about kind of the, while I'm prepping,
the game itself originally came out in, excuse me,
February 14th, 2003 in Japan
and in North America that next month in 2003.
And not only was it an excellent ergonomic shape
because you could fold the screen and things like that,
but it was able to then upgrade
with Game Boy Advanced SP Cart
or Game Boy Advanced Cartridges,
which just the color popped a lot more.
You didn't have to worry about batteries any longer
because it's all an internal battery.
And by the way, the internal battery's in great shape.
It's not bulging as you can kind of see on the camera.
It's just flat, completely.
Um, and this is all stock as well
as you can probably tell by the wear and tear.
So let's go ahead and pop in a copy of Pokemon Ruby, uh,
Ruby version while we test this out.
And lemme go ahead and look at the chat,
see if there's any questions.
Does Ruby version come with it?
No, it does not, unfortunately.
Um, has there been any modifications made? No.
And is there any accessories that come with the system? No.
So this is just the system itself.
Of course it will come with a charger.
I believe the chargers the same for the sp as well as it is
with the Nintendo ds.
However, uh, the Ds that is going to be showing is going
to be the DSI, so I'm not a hundred percent certain if
those two are compatible.
Uh, no, it would appear not based on the charging
ports themselves.
So if you have the original, uh, Nintendo DS
where it has this kind of, uh, thicker kind of a power port,
then yes, you'd be able to do that as well.
So let's go ahead and pop, turn this on just
to make sure you can hear sound
okay
now, if the camera would focus a little bit, please focus.
There we go. So the internal clock has run out on this game.
This, this one needs to be replaced for the battery.
Um, however, uh, the safe file is still there, so
luckily that's cool.
However, even though the game is not for sale, the sale,
the safe file is still existing.
So the Game Boy advanced SP cartridges for,
or Game Boy Advanced cartridges, were a little bit better
and handling that compared to the Game Boy Color cartridges.
So as you can see, uh, everything is working on the system.
The A button works, B button works, um, select
and start get out of this menu
and then select, we can't use the registered device.
It's probably the bicycle and the dpad all work as well
as the backlit screen.
So everything is working on the system, uh,
like I just had mentioned before.
Oh, I see a question about audio. Yes, of course.
Let me, lemme test the audio for you.
Hopefully you can hear it. Yeah. Okay.
I'm hearing people can hear it. Yeah. Okay.
I could adjust it. Yep, I just saw a question about that.
That's completely quiet. And this is Max volume. Yeah. Okay.
So yeah, people are able to hear it. Fantastic.
So in terms of, uh, text specs
for the Game Boy Advance sp while I'm just kind of waiting
for some more questions, we've got the 32 bit arm 70 TMI
processor as well as a s has a more impressive graphics.
And so, uh, graphics card basically allowing
for smoother gameplay as well as a, like I had mentioned
before, the front lit, uh, the built-in front lit, uh,
screen, as well as adjustable brightness.
And of course, um, it's able to play essentially any type
of Game Boy advanced game from any region
because up until the Nintendo DS all Nintendo consoles
were region free.
And we'll get into that a little bit more with the DSI.
So I, I am seeing a question.
Does this game, does this work with Game Boy games? Yes.
So the Game Boy Advance SP is fully compatible all the way
back to the original Game Boy.
Um, and the Game Boy color,
we gotta bring this back in as well.
Uh, the Game Boy Color also works
with original Game Boy games and Game Boy Color Games.
The Game Boy Advance SP works with Game Boy Game Boy,
color Game Boy Pocket,
which I don't believe there was a difference
between the games and Game Boy Advance Games.
I'm not seeing any more questions about the sp
so I will just go ahead and shut this off
and we'll move on to the next console.
Excellent. Okay, so, uh, for the next console it is going
to be the Nintendo DSI.
So this is the Japanese cop,
or excuse me, the Japanese copy,
which was released on November 1st, 2008 in Japan
and in North America and April 5th, 2009,
so about a year later.
So it was definitely the same family as a Nintendo ds.
However, uh, keep in mind this is the DSI
and it is a Japanese copy of a Nintendo handheld console.
And what does that mean?
Well, that means that you cannot play, unfortunately, um,
American Games for the Nintendo DSI.
So there are some differences
between the DSI games versus the DS games.
So Nintendo DS games, you can play on any system
across any region, the Nintendo DSI,
which is a huge distinction.
So if you're planning on buying this to play your DS games,
make sure you're aware that the can only play the Japanese
copies and vice versa.
So the American dsis can only play the nten,
the American Games, not the, the other region bound games.
So important distinction,
but, uh, we can talk about
that a little bit more later if there are any questions.
And you can also be sure to look it up on the Wiki
for any other few more questions.
So the cool thing about the DSI is
that it was first released with, uh, dual cameras.
So as you can kinda see the front facing camera
and then the back camera right here, um,
it also f featured the first DSI shop, which, you know,
the E shop's huge thing.
Nintendo Switch Shop, uh, a big deal for digital games
as well as being powered by dual arm processors
and features a dual 2 56 by 1 92 pixel screen,
so it's even bigger and better than the
original Game Boy color screens.
Um, so the cool thing is, uh,
it is a fully Nintendo DS system
or maybe not cool depending.
Um, so it can only play Nintendo DS cartridges,
however, it cannot play Nintendo GBA.
So if I have a fact, I do have one.
So I have an original Nintendo DS console here.
So as you can see, it can play the DS games as well
as the GBA games.
And also I had mentioned before about the sp it has the same
charging port as the Gable Advance sp
however, the DSI has a way nicer screen in terms
of quality between the two systems
and then, um, can only play the DS games
so it can play both DS and DSI games.
Uh, you don't have to worry about that,
it just cannot go past a previous generation of the console.
So let's go ahead and turn this on
and looking at the quality of the system itself.
So this is probably one of the nicest shaped consoles
that I have available today.
Uh, the game boy color was probably in second place.
This one is in pretty much pristine condition,
so I'll be sure to include a stylus, don't worry.
But the game card slot is fine.
Um, there's no problems there.
The door is not wonky
or anything like that internal battery,
and it is flat as you can kind of see, so you don't have
to worry about any bubbling
for the internal battery going bad as well as a headphone
and port 3.5 millimeter jack, as well as the game card slot.
Excuse me, I I had said this was the game card slot.
I meant this was the SD card slot,
which does include an SD card,
so you're not gonna have to worry about that.
And the game card slot is in great shape as well.
So the shoulder buttons are also working as well.
The hinge is tight
and responsive, probably hear the clicking.
Um, and then we'll go ahead and turn the console on itself.
I'll wait for any questions. Oh, the screen?
Yeah, you wanna, yeah, you okay?
You wanna see the screen operational? Yeah, apologize.
I always really love talking about the DS consoles, so, um,
as you can see, it is in Japanese, so please keep
that in mind as you are playing the games.
So you're able to play DS of region free games
as I'm seeing some questions about
the which games you can play.
Yes, you can play in the Nintendo ds, uh,
games from any region inside this game.
For DSI, it can only be based on the region
that the console is from.
So meaning we will show with a tester is Pokemon
White from Japan.
So this is a DSI specific game.
It cannot be played on American systems.
However, Pokemon like Platinum, Pokemon Pearl
and Diamond, which are Nintendo DS games can be played
that are American or English based,
can be played on a Japanese system.
So a little bit of confusion there,
but Nintendo stopped kind
of doing the whole region free systems, uh, past this point.
So the three Ds will be the exact same issue.
Uh, just maybe a little more clear
because it's only three DS games.
So let's go ahead and pop in a copy
of Pokemon White for the Japanese version.
Just go ahead and pop that in there. And as you can see,
the menu is responsive
and I'll make sure to turn up the volume,
which is just some buttons and it's working.
Great. And while
that's booting up, I'll wait for any questions.
It's come with any games. No,
unfortunately all the consoles do not come with games.
Does it come with any accessories? No, it does not a case.
No, it won't come with a case,
however, it will come with a
charger, so you don't have to worry about that.
Um, so the system is quite loud,
so I don't think you're gonna have to
worry about anything like that.
So lemme go ahead and turn that down.
Um, but as you can see, the screens are crystal
clear in terms of quality.
I mean it's, it's huge and above
and beyond what some of the other screens were like.
So this is just, uh, a different save file.
It's asking me to turn in the cge.
I, I know this because I've played the
American version quite a few times.
So lemme just go ahead and just press B on that.
Uh, okay, maybe I'll just have
to say yes or oh, that's right.
There's, uh, two different dialogues.
Lemme go ahead and wait. Uh,
any defects or problems with the screen?
No, I mean there, there is some like, like a little bit
of wear of course like on like the, the dpad
and as well as the buttons when you're pressing down.
Um, of course the screen, I'll be sure
to clean the sc the screens
before I even, uh, send it off or anything like that.
So no worries about that. Uh, can you test the cameras?
Yes, of course I can test the cameras.
Let me go ahead and show that the game itself is working.
So the dpad, no problem. And open up the menu.
We can be sure to press the B button, anything like that.
And we can also be sure to open up anything like that.
Start select, all those things are working fine.
So someone had asked if I can show off the cameras.
Yes, of course. Lemme go ahead and shut off the system
while it's booting up.
I'll wait to see if there's any other questions.
It seems like, seems like people are just talking about the
region, region bound.
Yep. So, okay, let's go ahead and take a look at the camera.
So I'm assuming it's this app.
Um, I don't speak Japanese or I can read
or even write in Japanese.
Um, so, or I could speak just the very bare minimum.
Um, but I'm definitely not fluent.
Um, so the problem is I believe it would require an SD card.
So I don't have one offhand.
However, uh, I did test the cameras when I first purchased
this system while I was in Japan.
And yes, the cameras are working properly
and I can show you the cameras on the three DS xl.
That's will be next because
I actually have an SD card in there.
Okay, which is kind
of a segue now into the next console is the Nintendo
three DS xl.
So this console is Nintendo's last.
Well, I don't know if you wanna consider the switch
to be handheld, but, uh, it is kind of Nintendo's last bit
of a hurrah in terms of a camera.
So please don't mind the glare. This is my microphone.
So as you can kind of see the, the, the microphone itself.
So, uh, the three S XL was released in Japan
and North America on July 28th, 2012.
So it features a dual core arm 11 processor, 120 megabytes
of ram, and a much more powerful GPU and larger screen.
So I believe I have, yes, so this is not for sale,
but I have the original three Ds as well.
And look at that screen comparison difference,
it's huge compared between the two.
Um, I mean, for me, I have, I don't have very large hands,
but even for me, the, the,
the original three DS was just, it was too small in my hands.
Yeah, I'm, I'm seeing some comments about people saying
like, you know, looking at the, the screen difference
between the two and I, once I started playing again,
I had this firm when I was traveling, um, just
because I was going to some kinda, some tough areas.
And this one is just so much nicer to play.
Once I got this, I upgraded
and I just, I just put this on a shelf
and haven't looked back just
because it's just so much bigger, so much nicer.
The buttons are so much larger, um,
and the screen is much more vibrant.
Uh, no, no, the, the original three Ds is not for sale,
but I saw some interest for
that, but no, that, that's all right.
Yeah, yeah. So yes, so, um, uh,
the cool thing is this is the first 3D based console in
terms of availability.
Um, personally I never used it a lot,
however, I can show you that it is working, I hope.
Uh, some of the Pokemon games are not 3D really enabled.
I don't have a copy of X and Y with me.
Um, and we can kinda show off the game in a little bit,
but I wanna show off the condition of the console, uh, just
because, uh, a reminder, again, this is a Japanese copy
of the Nintendo three DS extra large.
They called it the LL in Japan,
but it's the extra large, the xl.
Um, so it is a Japanese copy.
So keep in mind that it cannot play American based games.
It can only play three Ds games from the region it's from.
So in this case, it can only play Japanese three DS games.
If you had an American console,
you could play American based three DS games.
So kind of initially looking at the condition
of the console, there are some scratches in terms
of on the shell itself.
So you would probably need to get a cover
or replace the shell if this is bothering you.
Um, on the back as well, there's some wear
and tear, there's some markings here
as well as kind of like right here.
Uh, it's, it's been through quite a bit, you know,
three DSS were extremely popular in Japan,
so I'm sure this has been
through quite a few different journeys.
Um, the SD card slots does have an SD card in it, sorry,
was pointing at the microphone.
Um, I'll be sure to include a stylist as well.
The wireless buttons are working properly, same
with the three DS slider itself,
and then the shoulder pad buttons are working as well.
And it also does use the same charger as the DSI.
So that is a one thing to note. Um, no, no, no, no.
I, I'm seeing some questions about the, if you were
to use a charger with an American version system versus a
Japanese system, no, you're not
gonna have to worry about that.
Um, of course the plug might be a different type of plug,
but from what I remember, I believe it's the same type
of plug as the Japanese systems
or as the, I believe in Japan
and America, they have the same, the power scaling might be
different, but from what I remember, I think they charges
are the, are fine to use, uh, interchangeably.
So the volume wheel is also working.
And then the 3.5 millimeter headphone jack.
And then let's go ahead and open up the console itself.
So, uh, the, uh, circle pad is working fine,
the three DS slider
and the buttons are all responsive and not sticky.
So let's go ahead and turn on the console
seeing some questions about the, the camera itself.
Yes, don't worry. I will be sure to show off the camera.
Ah, there we go. Okay, so yes, so let's go ahead
and, yep, let's go ahead and ignore any news.
Let's go ahead and open up the camera first
and then I'll pop in a copy of Pokemon Moon to kind
of show off the gameplay
question about volume.
Yes, yes, of course. I will turn up
the volume, turn it down.
So let's see. Ooh, okay.
Oh, the 3D effects is in play, so, oh,
well that was making me sick.
Okay, so as we can kinda see the front facing camera, oh,
you can see a copy of Pokemon Moon right there
is working as intended.
You know, someone's like, hold up two
fingers, hold up your hands.
Yep, yep. You can see my hand
and then I will swap the camera.
It's taking a little bit. Ah, there we go.
Okay, so you can kind of see that. You can see myself.
Hello, I'm waving. Um,
and you can see that the camera is working.
Of course, it's gonna be a little laggy, you know, just
because it's just a different console.
Um, and then I will turn on the,
I don't know if you're gonna be able to tell the 3D effect,
but it is fully 3D oh,
and it is making me a little nauseated.
As you can tell, I never really fully had, uh,
the three DS effect enabled.
So, um, yes, it is, it is working.
Maybe you can see it that way. Uh, no you can't.
Uh, maybe okay. But yes, the 3D effect is working.
Um, so if you'd like to experiment with
that, absolutely go for it.
I think that would be a fun thing to do.
It just always made me a little sick to use it.
So, uh, I played the games for, uh,
or I played the consoles for the games.
Um, but yes, I'm, is the ees shop still working?
No, unfortunately they shut down the Nintendo ees
shop a little while ago.
Uh, so whatever you have on the
console is what you're gonna get.
Uh, unfortunately, uh, this is a clean slate copy.
Um, I'm not sure what would happen if you were to sign in,
if you had a three DS in the past
and you wanted to download games.
I believe the games themselves are also region bound, so,
um, even if you signed in with an American account,
I'm not sure what would happen if you were to do that
with a Japanese three DS xl.
I'm seeing some other questions. Can I port over?
Yeah, so we just answered that.
And does it come with any accessories?
No, and no other games as well.
Um, so I'm just using these games just to kind
of test the consoles, but unfortunately, um,
the games are not for sale themselves.
If you are interested in some of the games that I have,
yes, be sure to reach out.
Um, maybe, perhaps we can,
we can do a version with that later in the future.
So this is a brand new copy.
So, uh, remember all the, uh, Nintendo
or perhaps you don't know, uh, all the Nintendo copies, uh,
they do not save the data on the console themselves.
They save it on the cartridges.
So the cartridges themselves are what have the save data.
So in this case, this is a blank slate,
so it's not like there's something wrong
with internal memory of the system or there's no SD card.
Uh, it's just someone had reset this, uh, when they sold it,
because I purchased this in Japan when I
was there last year.
So the cool thing about the Japanese games,
however, for three DS is you can change the language
so you can actually play the games and of language
and your desired language, including English.
So, so even though this is a Japanese copy of the game,
you can play this game in English on a Japanese three DS xl,
as you can kind of see right here.
So that's one of the cool things.
Um, just to kind of show off the three DS XL again, uh, oh,
lemme go ahead and turn on the volume.
I'll let this play for a little bit while ask any questions.
It's a little glaring. Can you turn off the lights?
Yes, of course. How is that a little better?
A little worse. Okay, let, let me, uh,
lemme just turn down the, uh,
the lighting a little bit then.
Oh, pretty low as is. Uh, oh, there we go.
I'll just make it a little brighter. Okay. That better? Yes.
Okay, that's better. Okay, cool. Fantastic.
I'm gonna go ahead and turn down the volume a little bit.
So yes, everything is responsive.
Um, I'll try to get into the game really quick so then
that way we can kinda show off the circle
pad and all the buttons.
Are there any other questions?
Um, I'm not seeing any other things. The 3D effect?
Yes, so I don't believe they enabled that
for the Pokemon games, just
because these were also released on the Pokemon,
on the Nintendo two dus.
If anyone remembers that, it's the flat version
of the three Ds, but there's no 3D capabilities.
Um, I think they, they did that with
that intentional purpose.
However, there's a lot of 3D game, Pokemon game,
or excuse me, three DS Nintendo games,
3D Nintendo games out there
that allow you to do such a thing.
So let me go ahead and just, unfortunately the,
the newer Pokemon games, there's a lot of, uh, handholding.
So they kind of, lemme just, let me just, do you know,
random stuff, exclamation points.
Sure. I'm not gonna say this anyways, so just
for demonstration purposes.
Um, so go ahead and answer any other questions.
Is the touch pad on the bottom responsive? Yes, absolutely.
Let me go ahead and show that off once I'm able
to get into the game and show off the touch pad.
Uh, I guess I should have mentioned that the two Ds,
the two Ds or the DSI also has a touch pad
that is responsive on the bottom screen as well.
Maybe I can show that off too while I'm waiting.
Get both of these in view a little bit.
Eh, it's close enough.
So as you can see, I can click on different things.
I, I will clean this, don't worry. Sorry.
Probably is bothering some people that I'm using my finger,
but I don't have the stylist on me off end.
There will be a silence included, so don't worry.
We'll go ahead and boot up the game.
Okay, so hopefully, I think we're about to get started.
It always takes a while with the newer generation of games.
Oh, maybe not. Oh yeah, there's more story.
Okay, well you guys are stuck here for a little bit more.
Uh, so lemme go ahead and answer some more questions.
Um, there's a play other games aside from Pokemon.
Yes, so I'm just demonstrating with Pokemon Games,
it's my favorite, uh, franchise to play.
So that's just the reason why, uh,
but it's also an easy indicator just
because a lot of people know about Pokemon
and the different, uh, generations and regions.
So go ahead
and start this, go
through the train conductor scene again.
I wish there was a way to skip. Can you skip the cut scenes?
No, unfortunately you cannot skip the cut scenes, um,
and emulators, which I do not.
You know, I, uh, we won't go into that, uh,
but there are some fast forward
features that you're able to do.
So let me go ahead and continue. Onward blah, blah, blah.
And then lemme go ahead
and just skip past this just
to show off the two Ds touchscreen.
Lemme open up the menu and Pokemon
and then we can click on the different
summaries and things like that.
So the, the bottom touchscreen is working.
Um, I hopefully will be into the game soon
for on the right hand side.
And if you close the system, of course it's going
to pause the game as well, which is one
of the nice things about the Nintendo consoles.
Wanna answer some more questions?
We're about to wrap up soon.
Um, so if you're interested, be sure to kind of be sure
to check out the details that I've listed for each product.
Make sure that you click on them, review them.
I've included some mini videos as well as some screenshots
of the cons conditions.
So if you have any questions, please, please,
please be sure to let me know.
Um, does this come with a charger?
Yes, this does come with a charger.
Every console will come with chargers, except
of course for the game boy color.
This will not come with any con any con any, um, excuse me,
chargers because it takes AA batteries.
So that's the only one that will not come with that.
Um, I can include some, some batteries if you'd like.
Uh, however, I don't, I know some people are very particular
with the type of batteries they use.
I'm just using the, the Costco Kirkland branded batteries.
However, uh, you're more than welcome
to use whatever AA batteries you'd like.
Um, but every other console will come with a charger.
Yes, of course. Um,
lemme see if there are any more questions.
The condition of the 3D SXL again, can you show it?
Yes, of course. Uh, so I,
I'm just gonna be pausing the cut scene.
Um, so again, the shell has some
scratches on it on the front.
I would say the front is probably in its worst shape.
Um, the cameras themselves are working fine, um,
but there's just some markings kinda see here.
It's been, it's been through quite a bit.
Um, not as bad shape of the SP for sure,
but uh, it does have some markings here and here
and some shoulder pad buttons that are also working as well.
So there we go. Hopefully we will get to gameplay soon.
So then that way I can actually start showing the
buttons that are working.
Um, and I think of what else that you would like to know.
Um, oh yes, I think, hey,
I think we're about to jump in it soon.
Um, this was probably one of my,
actually I took a long break from Pokemon for a while,
I think after about gen three.
Got back into gen seven.
Someone had asked me what my favorite Pokemon gen was.
Uh, I would say, uh, Pokemon, uh,
gen two jo to was my favorite.
Um, I know, I know it's a, it's a pretty
millennial based answer, but it,
I I've started playing even like back in gen one,
but just gen two had both, you know, Jo to
and Canto, so absolutely amazing.
Okay, so we finally have control over a character.
So let's go ahead and move around.
So as you can kind of see the circle pad works, the dpad is
for Ride Pokemon in this game, so I can't show that off.
Maybe I can show that off in the home menu. Let's see.
This should, sometimes it takes a bit just with these games.
Yes, so the D pad is working just fine, um,
including like start
and select that is also reserved for other things as well.
To open up the menu, it's press X,
but I can show at least the touchscreen so
I can hit options, can change different things.
I can go back and it's a lot more responsive than the,
the DSI just, it's just better tech at the time.
Um, but as you can see, yeah, it's working great.
So I'm, I'm not seeing any other questions.
I'll give it a little bit more.
No, okay, so I think that is about it.
So lemme go ahead and do this. So there you have it.
So we've got four really amazing Nintendo, uh, consoles,
kind of really defining a legacy across a different years.
It's not every single one,
but remember it's the, the Game Boy color.
It's the Game Boy Advanced sp the Nintendo DSI
and the Nintendo three DS xl, the latter two, the DSI
and the three DS XL are both Japanese copies,
so please remember to remember that.
Um, but however you can play some of the Japanese games
that you have on your consoles and which is a cool thing
because sometimes the Japanese games are cheaper than the
American counterparts just 'cause they're in Japanese.
But you can play the, especially like the Pokemon games,
there are some three Ds games.
You can select the language to play in English.
So even though you have a Japanese copy, uh,
console does not mean you can't play games in English if
that is the language you wish to play it in, as well
as some other languages.
So, uh, make sure to add them to the cart, make sure
to review them, because remember, quantities are limited.
I only have, of course, you know,
this is the only quantity of each one.
Um, but I also do have some other consoles as you can kind
of see in the background behind me that will be going on
for sale later on at a date.
So be sure to check back if you're interested in, like,
for example, like the second dream.
Uh, nope, nope. Yeah, there we go. Nope.
Uh, uh, yeah, there we go.
The second dream cast as, or the, the game cube as well.
So if you're interested in those, be sure to let me know.
Stay tuned and yeah, feel free
to make sure you follow this channel or more retro gaming
and other product finds.
So I think that's about it, but, uh, we'll see you soon.
Thanks.