[Music]
all right you got lunch tomorrow at
12:00 uh-huh uh we have to do another
shoot over there in West Hollywood okay
uh then you got sneaker shopping
tonight I got sneakers shopping
tonight how could I
forget let's
[Music]
go
wao
yo
hello Joe we doing the show yeah let's
do the
show
what's up everybody it's Joe from
complex we're in La at Flight Club with
the Grammy and Emmy awardwinning Justin
Timberly how you doing I'm great going
to do some sneaker shopping tonight
going to see what he's feeling what he's
not and then hopefully he's going to buy
some sneakers let's do it man let's
[Music]
go when this happens that means Joe's
ready to get that yeah yeah
is Joe's I'm ready move talk about
it before we get to Jordan the shoes I
want to talk about Jordan the person and
you looking up to him what was it like
you know seeing him playing in the ogs
and like before even like you got to
design the player gosh yeah I have
posters of MJ on my walls growing up in
Tennessee and and not having access to
sneakers as much as you know a huge
metropolitan area right you know I would
have to say find a way to save up okay
to go to Foot Locker to wait in line and
I used to every
cutting grass okay on on my street with
everybody so I could try to you know
save money up 10 bucks a lawn and I
would I would try to save up and save up
to go wait in line at Foot Locker and
I'll never forget when the the black and
around Olive nines maybe yeah yeah yeah
when they came out like we all wanted
those so good such an underrated pair
underrated pair well and also growing up
in a rural area it was a sneaker you
could wear and not feel so bad if it got
well it kind of looks like a Timberland
that's
yeah totally which when they winterized
that shoe I was like what took them so
long who who just thought of this right
before we're going to talk a lot of
Jordans but I really like early 2000s
cuz you were Weare ing kind of like Cool
Air Maxes you were really in like your
Air Max bag air max 98 oh yeah what
about like that Air Max era what do you
remember about that well it's kind of
ironic that the two sneakers that had
the most effect on me when I first saw
them were the threes okay and Air Max
yeah and same
find out that the same guy yes was
behind was the genius behind yeah your
boy now yeah well yeah yeah I have a
story yeah but yeah I went through a big
Air Max phase just because like super
comfortable shoe yeah um I have big
arches in my feet okay so I would wear
them on stage when I could because they
were they just supported my feet and
when they used to you know when they
first sold them they came with the
little the little wedge yep I remember
all this the arch W it was a styrofoam
it was blue and pink like that
to really save the arch you just threw
them out you threw them out with like
the gel that you can't eat the little
things that are pois I I I would spend
so much time trying to put them the
right way in the yeah so another moment
Big Pop Culture moment big Music Moment
do you know the significance of these do
you remember oh God think about
it where did I wear these byebye bye
video matching think the whole crew
matched that's right whole crew indiglow
14s 2000 they came out you matched them
up yeah and that's why in sync is the
greatest boy band of all time
we go there we go but like was Jordan
brand seating you guys or were you going
out or do you remember complex rated
like the best moments in music videos
and that made it oh wow it's definitely
like a sneaker culture moment this is a
deep cut this is like a bide on a Stevie
Wonder Al you know what I mean like gosh
you're right and we all had them very
good to dance and good com shoot and
then another thing I like back in the
day celebrity games charity games you
always brought it you always brought you
always brought it and it was like you
were wearing
shoes that like Dirk nitzky was wearing
right right so like and true blue 3es
what about those games that you remember
like I'm definitely going to wear dope
sneakers yeah yeah well also too I was a
big Penny fan okay Memphis right big
Penny Hardway fan getting the deposits
were were like a big deal too okay but I
never I don't think I ever was I could I
could ever find the blue and black was
always the white oral yeah the original
I think I was just at that time I was
mixing it up and wearing just like
anything that caught my eye got it
boxes coming in at that point uh no not
as much not as much not even for the
videos you think costume designer or
yeah my my yeah maybe okay yeah like if
there was a stylist or something we were
able to get what had just come out at
the time okay but um yeah yeah I I not
the plug that I have now okay
[Music]
okay we want to talk Legends Of Summer
Don't Throw yeah well I'm going to catch
you could throw Legends Of Summer these
are two yes yeah so this wrapped up yeah
one two three yeah yeah so we did we did
an all red one
this I don't even know how to describe
it we called them the Dorothy they look
like the the red slippers you know it
literally like somebody littered them
you know what I mean and um and yeah I
really wanted I mean the three has
always been one of my favorite shoes and
the two to me has always been the most
underrated that's what a lot of people
say of Jordans that's just my personal
opinion and so the color of this shoe is
actually the uh exact same color of the
stage Jay and I have put together for of
the summer so when I
stage it actually like almost
camouflaged itself makes sense and um if
you kind of look down on the bottom it's
got a reference to suit and Thai which
which was a song at that time suit and
Tai and holy grail and yeah I wanted all
different materials on all the pieces of
architecture of the shoe so and the
shoes you know we couldn't even Source
them you had to bring them you had to
bring them well yeah as you I said you
have them our friend mayor who had the
ones he hooked up the the two-color one
but you bought them from home because
these stores
sneaker doesn't even have them but you
also said you don't even have that many
pairs they're going for like $20,000
what happened to all your pairs I know
well a lot of my boys a lot of my
friends we had same same size okay so
when when uh you know Jordan brand made
me my sort of stash yeah of of them I
just wanted to share with all of my
friends and I think I literally only
have one pair of the all red ones wow at
home got to keep those I know I will it
will
[Music]
yeah all good Joe I'm good you're living
on the
don't think I ever dropped one wow I'm
going to drop the next one you just
that's like he hasn't miss a free throw
all night yeah CL
exactly we got to talk the Super Bowl
moment okay you debut these and this
pair is really special this is cuz these
right are but little different in the
details you if you notice these you get
the you get the Nike yes and this was
you know obviously if you know you know
it's you know if you know you know this
was the original design for the three
and that Tinker you know said you know
the jump
on its own and we should take the Nike
Swoosh off which I'm sure was very
controversial right conversation at the
time I I would not want to be in that
board meeting exactly but so we talked
about like what if we brought the
original design back for the Super Bowl
performance and I I said I'm good with
that as long as cuz it's the 3M but I
said but as long as it's the same color
as long as it's white cuz I wanted it to
be a detail and not like an overbearing
thing because that's how Tinker saw it
got it right
think they only made three pair of them
one for them to keep one for me to rock
and then one for me to stock so this is
the stock one and and the difference is
you get the date in the Super Bowl that
they were at and then they drop under 5
minutes they sell out what was it like
to see it s I mean you you were busy
obviously but
no Reggie Reggie from from Jordan hits
me and said the sneaker sold out and I
was like what he goes they sold out in 5
minutes I was like wait I was on
stage
so like the sneakers sold out quicker
then I could actually get back off the
stage and so yeah it was it was an it
was a cool moment and and even at that
time you know we were working on the man
of the woods kind of I call the Boot
three that's what I call it
right right yeah that so so it was funny
because two or three days before I
performed at the Superbowl I had a
meeting with with Mike a conference
meeting what was that like uh it was
great you know he said he really loved
what
thing with the man of the wood shoe was
I wanted it to feel like a boot I wanted
it to feel like that n little like a
winter Bo you know and um I was always
into the wallabies okay you know like I
was I was like how do we do like a
reference to the WABE so that's why we
did the leather laces okay you know and
obviously it came with the orange pop
that you could do as well but I just
wanted to have that sort of like boot
feel to it and the body of the of
shoe lends itself to that anyway yeah
but these are called the these are
called the higher hes which is a song
off that album and you know had a ET in
there and then you know on the inside
it's one Sho says is cruel and then the
other one says Fame is a lie love that
and also I want to talk about one night
in Beverly
Hills uh Barney okay that relates to
this a little bit okay is this a
reference yes yes
wow this is a reference and I see it and
I love it because it when you think of
like what goes into these designs you
think of
but a Sakai jacket at Barney's in
Beverly I had found this Sakai amazing
you know winter coat and I just love the
colors of it and I was like this feels
like the color palette to my my album
yeah and so yeah that was the coat that
inspired the shoe and I love it cuz
there's a little yellow on the hood and
there's even yellow in the eyelids yep
love that there's the there's orange
detail yellow yeah you got it man love
that going back just for a second to the
Super Bowl ones though you said you have
one to the the ones
stock one for them one to rock but you
were locked in but the C wait it's such
a sneaker head thing but I know I know
the that's why that's why I brought
those actually I thought maybe those but
those aren't the on right cuz no those
have zero creases okay the big I brought
that one big sneaker head thing but
listen you got the Super Bowl
performance that was a big conundrum for
me because I was like do I break these
in you know what I mean cuz I'm like am
I going to come off limping you know
what I mean or like
like the worst Tow Jam ever you went for
function I went well but only because I
had two hair okay you know what I mean
it's crazy cuz oh yeah you'll take an
Instagram photo and you're not like
tying your shoe all the comments are wow
the crease the crease the crease but
that's a major I feel like I do have to
defend myself right now there go there
was one for work and then there was one
that I was going to keep and uh another
thing yeah that was yeah that was funny
aggressive priest but you had another
one on Deck Tinker half
this we you know it's good that we're
ending here in this section cuz you said
that this was the first one the kid
cutting the grass you think this was one
of the first ones okay the first pair of
Jordans that I ever had I didn't buy
them they were they were given to me
okay and they were the fives with the
number on the heel okay this shoe there
was a girl that lived in The Cove of the
street that I lived in and she was like
2 years older than me I was in sixth
grade she was in eighth grade and she
was the
at our school and could who like wow for
real and I had the biggest crush on her
especially when I found out she had a
pair of Jordans she wore these Jordans
to play and so she literally gave me the
Sho what a story
off her feet that was the beginning of
story me collecting Jordans you had a
crush on her did you get the girl no
just the shoes the shoes okay okay I'm
doing all
right exactly last thing I want to talk
about another special project I think
very close to your heart Big Creek Golf
Club oh yes the first golf outing that
you
you got a special makeup three pairs for
a tournament and now that golf Club
doesn't exist anymore no no it's it's a
completely different well so my my
history with that golf club was public
course and my stepdad really loved Golf
and he kind of like birthed my my love
for I I was I was very like I was very
clear with him that I was like no I'm a
Hooper I don't play golf and so big
Creek Golf Club it was funny like as I
got older I found out that they were
going to shut the place down and kind
of
Condominiums and so we actually went in
and saved the golf club we bought it
okay and we turned it into
Miramichi uh which means a place of
happy Retreat all right right now I
ended up selling it since then because I
don't get to spend that much time in
them anymore that so that shoe is a
really really special shoe there's not
there's it was three different ones
right 11 like a airx one and then like
kind of like a typical golf shoe Yes Man
Joe you really are good at your job
thank you man this is a big one you know
this is a big one
one for us I appreciate it man yes Joe
has Joe has been after me for how many
years a a long six seven years yeah yeah
yeah so finally made it happens
absolutely but it's exciting because I'm
working on some stuff right now okay
with them just on the golf Side Golf is
popping for them right now you see
Jordan getting involved as well yeah so
I'm I don't want to say too much but
there's some classic um there's some
classic sneaker bodies that I'm I'm
pushing to get okay on the golf course
spiked up and everything
nice listen week of your album thanks
much for taking the time talked about
everything now as the easy part browse
the shelves see what you're going to
take home I think you might get some uh
shoes for the fam yeah yeah I'm try to
get some some some sneakers for uh for
my two sons let's do it
[Music]
yeah
so how can I help you out today all
right man I'm definitely going to get
some stuff for me mhm but let's start
with the kids first let's do Grinch and
reverse I definitely got the Grinch and
reverse Grinch for you okay this is a
special moment my my oldest son's uhoh
first threes so maybe we just do
the reimagine of course course
definitely got that for him let's do
matching so let's yeah let's do a real
matching for me got you yeah perfect and
then my younger one this he's like very
colorful colorful Vib so maybe the
Powerpuff but maybe if you have him in
like blue I definitely have the blue one
for him I definitely grab that for him
okay now to me okay I got to do the born
and raised oh big dogs got to do those
so it looks like you looked at
everything over here yeah yeah yeah I
think it's time to go to the big boy
section big boy section this
it I I got to do the lobsters but I want
to do the orange O classic got to do
that okay I got the Carolina yeah off
whites in the Air Force but I think I
got to do the lemonade lemonade all FS
can't go wrong with those okay got you I
don't see them
here and you know it's a unicorn pair
that I never really got a chance to
purchase you got the Red October I do
have the Octobers 10 and A2 yes sir just
for
you all right I'll take all
right find everything we need tonight
Justin uh I found everything I need and
more so yeah
did some jamming yeah I didn't mean to
it happens you got me all right let's
get your total ready for you all
right did I buy that many I I think so
so your total tonight we're looking at
22,4 with
14 do I need to take out a loan or I
think you got it I got it okay it'll be
right there for
you and we are good you want some help
back there man want help no not really I
was just offering you're just offering
being a nice guy about
it all
right
go you are all set my guy all right
thank you so much thank you
me I got more than what I needed thank
[Music]
you
so Justin came through told some great
stories got some new sneakers thanks so
much for taking the time long time in
the making yes sir W it was fun thank
you thanks so much make sure you check
out the new album everything I thought
it was out this week thanks again this
week let's
[Music]
go