What's up everybody? It's Joe from Complex. We're in LA at Flight Club with the Grammy and Emmy award-winning Justin Timberlake.
Going to do some sneaker shopping tonight, see what he's feeling, and hopefully buy some sneakers.
Before we get to Jordan the shoes, I want to talk about Jordan the person. What was it like looking up to him?
Gosh yeah, I had posters of MJ on my walls growing up in Tennessee.
I started cutting grass on my street... 10 bucks a lawn... trying to save up to go wait in line at Foot Locker.
I'll never forget when the black and Olive 9s came out. We all wanted those. Such an underrated pair.
It's ironic that the two sneakers that had the most effect on me were the Jordan 3s and Air Max. Same guy, Tinker Hatfield.
Where did I wear the Indiglo 14s? The 'Bye Bye Bye' video. The whole crew matched.
We want to talk Legends Of Summer. We did an all red one... the color of the shoe is the exact same color of the stage Jay and I built.
We got to talk the Super Bowl moment. This pair is really special because it has the Nike Swoosh... Tinker's original sketch.
Reggie from Jordan hits me and said the sneaker sold out in 5 minutes. I was like, wait, I was on stage for 12!
My thing with the 'Man of the Woods' shoe was I wanted it to feel like a boot.
I had found this Sacai winter coat at Barney's... that coat inspired the shoe's color palette.
The first pair of Jordans I ever had... there was a girl... she was the captain of our basketball team... she literally gave me the shoes off her feet.
So how can I help you out today? I'm definitely going to get some stuff for me, but let's start with the kids first.
Okay, now to me. I got to do the Born and Raised. Oh, big dogs. Got to do those.
I think it's time to go to the big boy section. Let's do it.
You got the Red October? I do have the Octobers... All right, I'll take 'em.
Did I buy that many? I think so.
So your total tonight, we're looking at $22,014. Do I need to take out a loan?
You are all set my guy. Thank you so much. I got more than what I needed!